Shout out to everyone who came to the In Amanda We Trust screening in Houston tonight.
I truly, truly appreciate y'all so much for coming through.
And I hope that you all will put inamandabetrust.com on your posts so that people know where they can go and find my documentary.
It was really awesome just to see how many folks came out, especially the moms and daughters.
Like the mom and daughter pair just touched my heart right there.
It touched my heart right there.
But so much dope energy, so much dope diversity.
All my brothers, it was great to see y'all in the room too.
And of course, you know my sisters, we all was in the building.
So again, I hope you put inamandabetrust.com in your posts and share with people that they should go and check it out.
It's only available for two weeks and it's a big freaking deal.
See y'all in Philly tomorrow.